Guide to the Records of the Office of Media Production RG.7.3.4
New York University Archives
- Series II: 2025 Accretion, 2001-2010; 5 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons; 118 Betacam_SP
  - NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll 2009 / NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll 12/18/09 -- Project #0641 -- Reel #4, 2009-12-21; cuid19258 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19258)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Opening Symposium / Exteriors/Artwork - Carpet, Lecture (1 of 4) -- Project #0643 -- Reel #1, 2009-11-11; cuid19259 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19259)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Opening Symposium / Lecture (2 of 4) -- Project #0643 -- Reel #2, 2009-11-11; cuid19260 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19260)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Opening Symposium / Lecture (3 of 4) -- Project #0643 -- Reel #3, 2009-11-11; cuid19261 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19261)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Opening Symposium / Lecture (4 of 4) -- Project #0643 -- Reel #4, 2009-11-11; cuid19262 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19262)
  - Stern Undergraduate Footage 2009-2010 / B-Roll Tisch Hall, Kaufman Management Center, Stern Exteriors, Lobby, Interiors -- Project #0647 -- Reel #5, 2010-02-25; cuid19263 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19263)
  - NYU College of Dentistry Mobile Dental Health Van 10th Anniversary Video / PS 307 Visit Van B-Roll cont'd, Interviews w/ kids -- Project #0649 -- Reel #7, 2010-11-18; cuid19264 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19264)
  - Spring In New York Video Fall 2010 / Spring in New York B-Roll, Washington Square Park, Soho -- Project #0682 -- Reel #4, 2010-10-18; cuid19265 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19265)
  - Spring In New York Video Fall 2010 / Rogan Kersh BRoll (exterior walking and into Puck and class BRoll) -- Project #0682 -- Reel #6, 2010-10-18; cuid19266 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19266)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement Ceremony 1999 -- Project #0098, undated; cuid19267 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19267)
  - NYU Commencement 2006 Deck H -- Project #0460 -- Reel #4, 2006-10-25; cuid19268 (Box 228, Betacam sp cuid19268)
  - NYU Commencement 2010 Deck F In @ 11;05;45 Clean Feed Tape 2 of 2 CH 1/2 - PGM -- Project #0675 -- Reel #2, cuid19269 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19269)
  - NYU Commencement 2007 / Commencement B-Roll Tape 1 of 4 -- Project #0531 -- Reel #1, 2007-05-10; cuid19270 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19270)
  - NYU Commencement 2007 / Commencement B-Roll Tape 2 of 4 -- Project #0531 -- Reel #2, 2007-05-10; cuid19271 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19271)
  - NYU Commencement 2007 / Commencement B-Roll Tape 3 of 4 -- Project #0531 -- Reel #3, 2007-05-10; cuid19272 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19272)
  - NYU Commencement 2007 / Commencement B-Roll Tape 4 of 4 -- Project #0531 -- Reel #4, 2007-05-10; cuid19273 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19273)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Block Challenge at Coles tape #1 -- Project #0548 -- Reel #43, 2008-04-11; cuid19274 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19274)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Block Challenge at Coles tape #2 -- Project #0548 -- Reel #44, 2008-04-11; cuid19275 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19275)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Greetings - Roubini, Okun, Galloway, Wisenfeld, Dean Corfman, Pugel, Carrine -- Project #0548 -- Reel #47, 2008-04-14; cuid19276 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19276)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Student B-Roll -- Project #0548 -- Reel #48, 2008-04-14; cuid19277 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19277)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Student B-Roll Passport Day -- Project #0548 -- Reel #52, 2008-04-14; cuid19278 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19278)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Stern MBA Flag Football at Chelsea Piers (1 of 2) -- Project #0548 -- Reel #53, 2008-04-28; cuid19279 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19279)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Stern MBA Flag Football at Chelsea Piers (2 of 2) -- Project #0548 -- Reel #54, 2008-04-28; cuid19280 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19280)
  - Global Network University Video / NYU B-Roll Compression shots, general NYU campus -- Project #0559 -- Reel #40, 2008-04-18; cuid19281 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19281)
  - Abu Dhabi B-Roll from Atlas TV -- Project #0559 -- Reel #51, 2008-05-15; cuid19282 (Box 228, Betacam sp cuid19282)
  - Global Network University Video / Abu Dhabi stock aerials from Atlas TV NTSC -- Project #0559 -- Reel #57, undated; cuid19283 (Box 228, Betacam sp cuid19283)
  - Global Network University Video / Abu Dhabi stock aerials from Atlas TV NTSC 4x3 letterbox -- Project #0559 -- Reel #58, undated; cuid19284 (Box 228, Betacam sp cuid19284)
  - Global Network University Video / Abu Dhabi stock aerial from Atlas TV -- Project #0559 -- Reel #62, 2008-08-01; cuid19285 (Box 228, Betacam sp cuid19285)
  - Administrative Management Council Video / AMC Meeting 4/6/10 -- Project #0658 -- Reel #6, 2010-04-06; cuid19286 (Box 228, Betacam sp cuid19286)